cactusglobal.com 2015-06-12

# Privacy Policy | CACTUS

This website is owned and operated by Cactus Communications Pvt. Ltd. ("CACTUS"). Throughout the site and in this policy, the terms "we," "us," and "our" refer to CACTUS. CACTUS offers this website, including all information and services available through this site to you, the user, conditioned upon your acceptance of all the terms, conditions, policies, and notices stated herein. Your use of this site constitutes your agreement to this Privacy and Terms of Use Policy.

All the information (“Content”) presented on this website is for informational purposes only and does not create a business or professional services relationship between you and CACTUS. (A service relationship is established only when you place an order through this site and is subject to the Service and Payment Terms , incorporated herein by reference.) While CACTUS will use reasonable efforts to provide reliable Content through this website, CACTUS does not warrant that this website is free of inaccuracies, errors, and/or omissions. This site may contain certain historical information, which is provided for your reference only. We reserve the right to modify the Content presented on this site at any time.

Links to third-party websites are provided for convenience only and do not imply any approval or endorsement of that site or service, even if they contain the CACTUS logo (or the logos of any of the CACTUS brands). CACTUS cannot be held responsible for the Content of any linked site or any link listed on this site.

The Content presented on this website (including but not limited to text, design, software, graphics, audio, video, html code, and buttons) is protected under the intellectual property and copyright laws of India, and is the exclusive property of CACTUS.

CACTUS reserves all rights to this site and its Content. This Content may not be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way, without the prior written consent of CACTUS. You may use the Content for personal and non-commercial purposes in accordance with the principles governing intellectual property law; you may download and print one copy of any material available for download solely for your personal, non-commercial use, provided that you do not modify the material in any way and you keep intact all copyright, trademark, and other proprietary notices. Any other use or modification of the Content without CACTUS’s prior written authorization is prohibited.

You may not use contact information provided on the site for unauthorized purposes, including marketing. You may not use any hardware or software intended to damage or interfere with the proper working of the site or to surreptitiously intercept any system, data, or personal information from the site. You agree not to interrupt or attempt to interrupt the operation of the site in any way. CACTUS reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to limit or terminate your access to or use of the site at any time without notice.

We may need to obtain certain personal information, such as your name, home or business address, and email address. Personal information is collected only when you choose to voluntarily provide us with this information. The main purpose of collecting such data is to process a service, partnership, or employment request made by you. When you submit such information to us, you represent that you have the lawful right to submit such information and agree that you will not submit any information unless you are legally entitled to do so. You may not use a false email address or other identifying information, impersonate any person or entity, or otherwise mislead as to the origin of any content. 

You acknowledge that such information provided by you may be copied, used, and stored by the relevant CACTUS representative in accordance with local data privacy laws but will not be disclosed to third parties who are not involved in processing your request. However, CACTUS reserves the right to retain information solely to resolve potential disputes and to disclose confidential information (i) as mandated by law; (ii) in connection with a court action brought by a client against CACTUS or any of its agents, employees, officers, directors, or service providers; and (iii) in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of CACTUS, its users, or the public.

**Use of cookies ******

The CACTUS website may use “cookies” to track users’ traffic patterns. A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser. These cookies are used to assist you in reaching the appropriate information; they help tailor your visit to your individual preferences. You are free to decline these cookies by altering your browser settings accordingly.

**Confidentiality of information**

CACTUS considers any and all information related to its clients to be strictly confidential.

The following measures prevent information disclosure: 

  * All our data security processes are ISO 9001:2008 certified and our IT security management systems are ISO/IEC 27000:2005-certified.
  * All our employees and contractors have signed confidentiality agreements and will not make any client information available to anyone outside CACTUS, unless authorized in writing by the client. 
  * We respect the privacy of our clients; therefore, their personal information (name, address, email address, contact number, etc.) will never be made available to any outside party. 
  * All documents submitted are managed through a secure online job management system; the documents that are sent to us as raw data for editing or publication support assignments can only be viewed by editors/publication experts working on your assignment and your customer service manager.
  * Your personal information is kept strictly confidential and CACTUS will never share it with external parties without your consent.
  * On request, we will also sign a confidentiality agreement with you before you submit your data to us.

**Website Security**

The CACTUS website uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption—the best online security available. This ensures that your personal information and files are secure. Our website is verified by VeriSign, the largest and most trusted certification authority online. For further details on security and encryption, please visit the VeriSign website.

 **Payment Security**

In order to protect your credit card information, all online transactions are conducted using a secure 128-bit SSL encryption signed by VeriSign. Encryption ensures that no information is accessible to unknown parties, so you need not worry about information theft. CACTUS will never store your credit card information, so there is no possibility of fraudulent charges. Please visit VeriSign’s website for more information about payment security.

We have also partnered with PayPal to provide you with the most secure and easy-to-use online payment system available. For information about how PayPal can protect you from unauthorized payments, visit PayPal’s website.
